Episode 5    Just the Way You Are
My minions.
Have you steeled yourselves?
Then I shall now present the
Princess Series monthly reports!
You have been evaluated on combat outcomes,
negative energy accumulation,
drive, enthusiasm, et cetera.
First on the overall leaderboard is...
Bear's team once again in a landslide!
Reaper Princess
Beast Princess
Their streak of breakaway leads over
the second-place finisher continues!
Reaper Princess is also very
aggressive in suggesting plans,
and she has a perfect
combat attendance record.
Truly, she is a role model for evil!
Beating Red half to death the other
day also earned her big points.
You could all learn a thing or two from her!
Reaper-san is very impressive.
Grr...
Could we have a word about
your first-place ranking?
I'm very pleased.
And to celebrate your achievement,
you receive a Super Bosslar-kun Doll!
This ain't gonna stand!
You think you can outshine me
every single damned time...
Let's settle this, Reaper Princess! You and me!
Please calm down.
You can have this, if you want.
I don't want the damned thing!
thonk
Cafeteria
Here you are! One pasta set!
Stupid Reaper.
I'll show her soon enough.
Next time, I'm gonna be number one!
I suppose we'll see.
Shut your hole, last-placer!
And what's that crap you're eatin'?
Pickled sea cucumber.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Beast Princess...
She appears to have some
kind of grudge against me.
She hates losing, and suffers
from violent mood swings.
Steel Princess.
She seems to exist in her own little world.
She's uncompetitive,
and she's hard to get a handle on.
Would you like a bite?
Hell no!
They're a fun little duo.
Would you hear me out, Beast-san?
I have something on my mind.
The truth is...
I've fallen in love with someone.
Like I give a damn.
Don't come to me with crap like that.
You can tell me all about it!
Butt out, Reaper!
You're in love? That's fabulous, Steel!
Reaper-san, are you interested
in people's love lives?
D-Didn't think you were the type...
So? What kind of person are they?
Terribly wild, yet very understanding.
Mmm
No one wants to see a Reaper
make that stupid, goofy expression!
But this person is technically a co-worker.
Hang on, you kiddin' me?
Workplace romances are off-limits.
Give it up already.
I know that my feelings are wrong.
Yet... I cannot stop myself.
Followin' the rules comes first.
Tell her, Reaper.
I understand.
I completely understand how you feel, Steel!
squee
Hey!
Who cares if it's against the rules?
I'll do everything I can to support you!
What's got you so enthusiastic?
Thank you, Reaper-san!
I said you can't do it!
Okay, Steel. What do you want to do next?
It's like they don't even hear me!
I'd like to tell this person how I feel.
Yeah, that sounds right!
You can't get anywhere until they know!
What's wrong?
I'm absent-minded, plain, and a poor worker.
I possess no qualities considered
appealing in a woman.
There's no way this person
would ever return my feelings.
Don't think that way, Steel.
I know you can make that confession!
But how?
With femininity!
We'll help your develop your femininity,
and give you the courage to
tell this person how you feel!
Soldiers in an evil army
don't need femininity!
Do you think I can do it?
Of course you can!
Don't worry. I'll help you!
Reaper-san...
I will try!
Cafeteria
That's the spirit!
Let's do our best, all three of us!
Since when am I a part of this?!
Hey...
Hey.
Hey!
Pilates are great for your mental
and physical well-being.
You have to concentrate, Beast!
I told you, I ain't part of this!
How are you feeling, Steel?
Okay, next up!
Terror
Next up...
The Beautiful Manners of Maturity
Femininity
Next up.
Next up!
This exercise will develop your
core muscles, giving you a great figure!
H-Hey, are you okay?
I've had enough.
These exercises have only served
to confirm how worthless I am.
I will give up on love.
Thank you for trying your best for me.
Hey, now.
I think you made her feel
even worse about herself.
Steel...
I'll get you this time!
Charge!
I see.
Sounds like you've been working really
hard to help your friend, Desumi-san.
Steel is just like I was.
No confidence in herself at all.
But I ended up getting ahead
of myself and hurting her instead.
I guess telling someone how you feel and
getting them to date you isn't that easy.
Hey, Fudo...
What do you expect out of
your significant other?
Nothing in particular.
Nothing?
As long as you're by my side,
that's good enough for me.
S-Stupid!
There has to be something!
Don't you want me to be
a good cook or anything?
There isn't.
I like you just the way you are.
H-Honestly... you're hopeless, Fudo.
Thank you, Fudo.
I'm a very lucky girl.
I just hope I helped.
Yeah. You really did, Fudo.
I forgot about something very important.
Steel Princess
Dressing Room
We're coming in, Steel.
Iron Labyrinth
She's been holed up like this a whole day now.
When she gets like this,
she refuses to budge,
and it gets dangerous to approach.
Stupid! Don't provoke her!
Her shell's system
counterattacks automaticall!
Listen to me, Steel!
I was wrong.
You never had to change!
It's okay to have things you're not good at!
You should be just the way you are!
Be the Steel that we know!
So, please, Steel...
Don't give up on love.
Just the way I am?
You didn't really give up, did you?
I didn't.
You didn't really want to
deny your feelings of love.
I didn't, Reaper-san.
Sheesh, what a pain in the ass.
Thank you, you two.
You've given me the courage I need.
I know that I'm incompetent,
and completely lacking in appeal...
But that's just
the way I am!
I'm going to tell that person how I feel!
Eensy-weensy
Eensy-weensy!
I'm gonna beat the shit outta you!
I hope that person blows you off!
Hang on... he's the one she's confessing to?!
And they're allowed to date?!
This is totally against the rules.
Every one of you, I swear...
I'm so happy for you, Steel!
Love After World Domination!
I'm grateful for this food.
It's on me.
Eat up.
You mean it?
That super-duper nice! Thanks tons, man!
In exchange, I have a favor to ask you.
Yeah, yeah.
I figured.
Sure thing, gotcha.
Allow me to borrow Steel Princess.
Steel Princess?
Sure thing!
Y-You mean it?
Totally, dude.
But she's pretty frickin' stupid. You sure?
Don't you say that about her!
Hang on, hang on!
You're scary when you blow up like that!
Take this, Gelato 5!
Waves of Love Attack!
Hang on! What's Steel Princess doing here?
I thought she was on a different squad!
What's going on here?
The power of love!
We don't have a choice.
I've got to call Red back!
Red-san isn't here!
B-But... I was sure he came this way...
He didn't!
But if you insist on coming this way...
You'll have to beat me first!
Quoi?!
This is like a bad dream.
Praise me! Praise me! Praise me!
Praise me
T-Thanks.
We appreciate it, Haru.
Oh, I know, Fudo.
Are you hungry?
You made us lunch, Desumi-san!
Mother!
Thank you for bringing me into this
world in the same era as Desumi-san!
Shove
It's really not that big a deal!
Let's eat—
Wait, Fudo!
What?
According to the specialist
texts I consulted,
when couples eat together,
they're supposed to... feed each other.
F
E
D
!!!
Feed each other!
Oh, I've heard of this!
At last, I'll get to see it done!
God above, thank you for creating this world!
Shove
C'mon, cut it out!
I feel like we're at about
the stage to try it.
Agreed. Let's advance to that next step.
H-Here it comes, Fudo!
Bring it on, Desumi-san!
O-Open wide!
O-Opening wide...
What is... happening?
What is it, Fudo?
My stomach hurts... like it's
never hurt before!
What did you say?!
Heave
Oh, come on!
This is no time for that!
Heave
These could be my last breaths...
Quickly!
I don't want to feed you this way!
And so... I die.
F-Fudo!
Haru! Emergency!
Days
Later
Machino Hospital
Dear Red Gelato,
We wish you a swift recovery.
If you are to die,
we hope it will be at our hands.
Gekko's Great Leader
Supreme Leader Bosslar
His doctor said he can go home tomorrow.
That's such a relief, Senpai!
But I guess appendicitis can take
out even the toughest among us.
I'm so sorry for all the trouble.
Now, none of that.
Just rest for now.
I peeled you an apple.
Want some?
Thanks, Misaki-neesan.
Open wide!
Opening wide...
O-Open wide!
No! Desumi-san must be
the first woman to feed me!
The heck are you doing, Fudo?
Open your mouth already!
Stop playing around and eat it already!
Chomp
You're both acting crazy!
Haru-kun!
Goodbye for now. Take care, Fudo-kun.
Yes, sir. I will.
See you!
Inpatient Building
Examination Room
Now, Fudo, open wide!
Desumi-san...
Opening wide!
I brought apples!
That was close!
Eh? What was close?
Oh... nothing, Mom.
I brought you a change of clothes.
Oh, thank you.
I'll leave the apples here,
so you can eat them later.
Well, I have volleyball
with my women's group!
Sure.
This must be some kind of karmic retribution.
All right.
Don't do anything stupid, Fudo.
You'll pop your stitches.
Desumi-san!
I heard they're letting you out tomorrow,
but I wanted to see you while you
were in this unusual situation...
squee
Oh so cute...
You seem to be feeling a lot better now.
The color's back in your face, too.
I'd never die until I let you feed me!
Shove
Don't talk big, Mr. Appendicitis!
You're hitting my stitches!
Honestly, you're just so silly.
Here, Fudo...
To celebrate your recovery.
Open wide!
Opening wide...
H-H-How did you like it?
No food since the dawn of civilization
has ever been so delicious!
Fudo...
Desumi-san...
I just remembered, Fudo!
Your father's coming to pick you
up in his mini truck tomorrow!
The mood!
Oh, is this a friend of yours?
Can you play volleyball?
We need more players to fill the team!
Come, come, come, come!
The mood!
Desumi-san!
Sudden Death Seniors
You were such a big help today, Desumi-chan.
It was my pleasure!
Call me any time you need me.
You know I will.
But I'm sorry for what I did earlier.
I know you were in the middle of feeding him.
A-Actually, I was...
No need to be shy.
Pat
I did the same thing with
my man back in the day!
Despite what you might think, I used
to be a real looker back in the day.
Want to see?
S-So cute!
Yes, yes!
I really was, wasn't I?
Desumi-chan, take care of my Fudo.
I will!
Secret Society Gekko has a combatant
cafeteria and dormitory facilities.
A mentorship system helps
to guide the inexperienced.
We treasure individuality in our work force
as we work together to
achieve world domination!
Episode 6    As Long as We're at the Beach...
Next time: "As Long as We're at the Beach..."
Secret Society Gekko
We'll be waiting for your resumes!